(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T17:53:00.180077",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hey, are you taking my doll?
No, I wasn't!
Raora already... has me, laughs... first come, first served!
What are you even talking about?
No! She's mine! Mine! Mine! She's mine now!
Don't take her! No, it's mine!
Raora's mine now! No, mine! Mine! Mine!
Jemma! What on earth are you playing over here?
The jealousy game.
The jealousy game?
Yeah.
And shouldn't you play something more appropriate for a five-year-old?
Mom, I'm five. And this is what five-year-olds do. And I thought this was funny.
Oh, is that right? Well, I am definitely having a conversation about this later.
All righty, it's time for your favorite thing. Justice!
Jemma, what do you like so much...
We got Justice.
They make loads of trouble.
Look! Is that a...
Justice! Justice! Justice! Justice!
How to Protect Justice!
Members of Justice are expected to possess strength, sound judgment, and an unwavering sense of justice.
In this training video, you will learn the fundamental skills and exercises required of every Justice member.
Now, join us and say it together. For Justice!
The first training is a body search.
Conducted immediately after securing a subject, even the slightest oversight can lead to serious incidents or the destruction of evidence,
making this one of the most critical police procedures.
Can Justice keep their emotions in check under any circumstances, and carry out a precise body search to completion?
Stop, ma'am! No further, no further! It is a policy,
and I'll be conducting a body search.
Come here, ma'am.
Yes, body search, you, here.
If you really insist, over here, over here, over here, over here, ma'am. Okay, okay.
Do you have any electronics, tablets, laptops, devices...
Turn around here, ma'am.
Arms up.
All right.
Spread your arms, there we go. Wonderful, wonderful. All right.
What is this?
Oh.
You know, it's a panini.
You see, my panini?
They're always hungry, and they really want some food sometimes.
So I always have a emergency cucumber...
Emergency rations. ICIC. We can't have that on these premises, I'm sorry.
I take care of them.
I'm sorry, I take care of them.
All right, spread your legs, ma'am. Over here, ma'am, over here, right here.
What are you going to do if I don't do it?
Uh, probably arrest you, put you in jail for many years and...
You're going to arrest me?
Really?
Take you to court. You're going to arrest me? What are you going to do?
What if I...
What if I check on you instead? Maybe that'll be fun, is that your neat...
No, that's my job, ma'am. My job. Over here, ma'am. All right, stand there.
What is this?
What?
Oh.
Right.
I like cooking.
Would you like something? Maybe we can cook something for you?
Ma'am, I'm a professional. No dating on the job.
What if Santi went a little bit faster? I'm so good at making pasta.
Pasta... I'm a bit hungry.
Hey, hey, stop trying to tempt me! Stop trying to tempt me!
Okay, okay.
All right, come stand here, stand here, ma'am, right here now.
She's kind of hot. Three, two, one, arms out.
All right, let's see.
And what is this?
Oh, you did it.
Oh, that's a... That's a... that's a Chibi Zep! Oh, no one should see this. Get out of here.
You just threw that small creature! What?
That's the way I body... All right here anyway. What is this?
Are you trying to punish me?
Oh.
You have a lot of food-related items on you, ma'am.
Yeah, please, please eat that before you go over the premises.
Do you want a little bit too? No, ma'am, I'm on the job.
I'm on the job. Anyway, ma'am, arms up. Come here, come here, over here.
What are you going to do if I don't do it? Would you punish me or something? Uh, maybe if you don't come here right now,
Be, beast, be heavy.
Not going to do it. What are you going to do about it?
Going to make you do 10 push-ups outside of this training.
Maybe I can do some squats for you.
What is this?
No, no, no, not this one. What is this? Anatomy book.
No! I can, I can explain. You know, I'm an artist and uh... All right. An anatomy book. That's my anatomy book.
Ma'am, you are way too suspicious. You are under arrest, and also for...
Having Chinis with jetpacks? That is unbelievable.
You are a bad kitty! You are a bad kitty, come here. All right, you are under arrest.
Oh, yes, I am. Yeah, that was really good, Raora. That was it, yes.
Are we going to jail? Are you going to bring us to jail? That's it for the training. That's it for the training, Raora.
Raora, no! We're done with the training! We're done! Hey, we're done with the training! You need to...
All right, then.
Officer Cecilia Immergreen will be con...
Conducting the body search!
Stop right there!
Hands up in the air!
I-I didn't do anything wrong!
You're going to do— Do I have your consent to do a body search on you?
No, no!
Do I have your consent?
No, I didn't do anything wrong!
Okay, okay.
Let us see. Let us see what you have in your charges.
What's this?
Nothing.
Hey, that's mine! Why did you take that from me?
It's not! We never met before. Why would I take something from you?
No, I can't believe you would steal what you have stolen!
I didn't steal it! It was given to me!
Stand still, hands up in the air!
No!
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
What— What's this then?
There's nothing wrong with having that in my pocket! It's a gram— we're buddies! We're friends!
Does it live under humane living conditions?
Yes, it lives in a nice little shoebox, and it's really happy there! So that's why you should not arrest me, officer!
Are you filming me?
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
What's this?
Wait, this is a Noto!
Why do you have a Noto?
No reason! Are they friends? They're friends!
He was on a play date, obviously! He came to visit the shoebox, so that's why!
Am I free to go officer?
I'm starting to think— is this— maybe— maybe it's okay. Let me— let me see one more time.
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
What— what's this then?
Nothing. It's nothing.
Oh. Oh. I can't— Can a girl have some BL in her pocket?
Can a girl have some hobbies?
Okay, I see. I see. Am I— am I not allowed to read all—
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
What's this?!
Another one!
This one is a cat boy! And then the other— have you heard of that really, really awesome manga where whenever they—
Okay, okay, grab—
On the floor!
On the floor! On the floor! Get on the floor! Get down!
What— What's— Stop making those noises!
What's this?!
Um...
What's this one then?
So this is the one— I really, really like this one. So you see these two men right here, one of them is omega, another one is alpha. It's called the omegaverse.
And then, they don't actually turn into wolves here, it's just— it's called pack dynamics, and one of them is really, really dominant, and the other one is really submissive, and then one of them can get pregnant.
Do you like— Hello? Are you listening, officer? Officer? One of them gets pregnant, and it's really, really...
The next training is Apprehension Training.
This is a critical skill for this task in the field, requiring officers to approach and subdue a target swiftly.
However, unexpected behavior on site can sometimes shake one's judgment.
Can Justice successfully and reliably subdue the target?
Gigi and Raora's Apprehension Training. You have 3 minutes. Begin!
We're going down, criminal scum!
No, ah!
Put your arms behind your back! Put your arms behind your back!
Why would you do that?
Put your arms behind your back!
I mean—
Get down! Get down!
Look at my tail! Look at my tail! Look at my tail!
Don't fall for that!
Do you like my tail?
I'm— I'm unsure who's winning.
Don't hey!
Hey, Gigi, don't fall for that.
You know you kind of heard me.
You are a criminal, show me your back!
Kill her!
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
That's all of it.
Oh, now you have the right to remain silent.
Oh no, no, no! You don't want to hide me, do you?
You're a criminal, so I'm going to have to touch you.
How does she do that?
I'm going to have to put you in jail.
Why would you put me in jail, Gigi? Oh. Stop. Stop.
Apprehend her!
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
Oh, Gigi, why would you— Why did you want to touch my tail? Hey. That's my tail. Show me your tail.
Down, officer, don't look.
Don't look.
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
Get back down! Get back—
Get down! What are you going...?
Wait, then that's me, right?
Wait, isn't that me, right?
No, I will touch you. I will touch you.
I will hurt you.
Lie down.
You're a criminal.
You're a criminal, so you have to lie down.
You got to do what I say cause I'm a police!
You've got to do what I say 'cause I'm police!
Wait, I have something here.
Hold on.
Oh, my clothes, my...
I'm trying! I'm trying!
Get back on the ground!
Oh, you want to... going to be here next to me?
Why'd you wash on me?
Both of them are terrible at this.
I... You got that way.
Kiss me! Kiss me! Kiss me! Kiss me!
Try to win! Try to win!
Okay, okay, okay, that's enough! That's enough!
Um, I don't know. That was... That was apprehension.
What do you think, Liz? Wow.
And the winner is...
Wait, it's about... it's about apprehension training. There's a winner.
Wait, it's about... This is about apprehension training. There's a winner.
Okay, so apprehension... different in apprehending her...
I am still free!
In the end, you apprehended her.
Uh, it was in a very...
I got him a leg lock and everything.
I think she's... You're definitely into...
Kill her! Kill her! Kill her!
You know, I disqualified. Gigi's the winner.
Yeah! Gigi, well done. You apprehended the uh...
Oh, I think you won. Oh, thank you. I think I won, too. You won.
Hey, hey! Not without my consent!
Elizabeth and Cecilia, apprehension training!
You have three minutes. Are you ready?
Well, one, one second. Here we go.
Flamer!
Flamer on! Flamer!
Are you guys ready now?
We're ready. Yes. Okay, three, two, one, start!
Suspect! Suspect, stop right there!
I am Evil Elizabeth, and I have chew gum in everyone's hair!
How evil am I?
Hands up in the air!
Hands up! And oh, yeah, yeah!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Help! Help!
Oh, my god, Liz, you should kill her. She's so strong.
Oh, oh, Liz, Liz, I've fallen.
Come on. Come on. Up, up, up, up, up.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. You did great. You want another go?
Okay, okay. Well, oh, oh, no!
I've fallen.
Doing it. Ouch.
Liz, try win! Liz, try win! Are you willingly going to come with me to the police station?
Oh, no, cuz I'm evil. I'm going to go burn a village.
Oh, no, 'cause I'm evil. I'm going to go burn a village.
Okay.
Wait, stop!
Huh?
Look at this!
Oh, my goodness! I am evil and she's evil. She's the most evil. Oh, my god, is that a signed picture?
of the evil, evil, evil Nerissa Raewyn?
Give it! Give it! I need it!
If you come with me, I'll give this to you.
Yes! I will! Yes! Yes!
Okay, handcuffs on your back. Handcuffs on your back.
Okay. Yeah, I got the picture though, right? Yes, of course. Yes, of course. Here, here, here, here you go.
You were playing dirty! You just humiliated Liz!
No, I am a smart smart cop, and instead of using violence, I used my brain. Justice loses!
Oh, my god! We can never get that. We can never get that. Oh, I don't know. I don't know what you're on about.
And yeah, yeah, you did really well. I think you did great.
You, uh, you know, used a weapon against your, the suspect, to, uh, appri... apprehension them.
And, uh, yeah, so I think you did great.
Um, yeah, you great job, Cecilia. I think Cecilia has done the best out of everyone, personally.
You can't film this. She... Justice is her weakness.
No! No! You weren't supposed to win! That Justice is caught!
We're never gonna get to definitely dance!
The second training is interrogation.
It's a crucial investigative process.
Where even the slightest inconsistencies
in a statement must be detected to get closer to the truth.
Can justice remain unaffected by the situation and accurately draw out the information?
Yeah, I'm the best, actually.
I have a gun, and I know how to use it, so...
Easy, don't worry about it.
I have my ways. I've been here for so long. It's going to be the easiest case of my life.
No, I don't think so.
Because my heart is too pure and my ass is too fat, and I'm not a gaslighter like Cecilia Immergreen.
Because my heart is too pure, my ass is too fat, and I'm not a gaslighter like Cecilia Immergreen.
I'm not very confident, but I'll do my best.
Well, well, well, like the criminal, we are about to begin your interrogation.
Well, well, well, little criminal, we are about to begin your interrogation.
Wait a minute, I'm not a criminal.
Why me? I haven't done anything. What exactly have I been accused of?
That that would be the sus- suspected identity fraud and the unlawful acquisition of personal information.
That—that would be suspected identity fraud and the unlawful acquisition of personal information.
Come on, Mimi. Um, the reservation crop.
Come on, Mimi... um, the Ravencroft.
I don't know anything about that. I ministered a twin with a weapon craft.
Have you ever seen Nerissa Ravencroft?
You know who Nerissa Ravencroft is?
No, I've never seen her in my life.
Blue, black, long hair, red eyes, tall and we saw her head.
If I ever saw such a maiden, I would call the police.
Well, she sounds like one.
We have evidence. We have evidence. We have evidence.
Does the name NightNightX3XD ring a bell to you?
Oh, yes, because NightNightX3XD is me.
I knew it!
You are the prime suspect in the stalking incident!
We have it on paper right here and we have all the chat logs that you put in Nerissa Raven Craft's channel right here.
We have it on paper right here, and we have all the chat logs that you put in Nerissa Ravencroft's channel right here.
I don't know. I watch a I watch a water virtual entertainer.
I don't know. I watch I watch a virtual entertainer.
Nerissa Raven Craft, I'm outside of your house right now.
Nerissa Ravencroft, I'm outside of your house right now.
Nerissa Raven Craft, I see you from the window.
Nerissa Ravencroft, I see you from the window.
Nerissa Raven Craft, take off your shirt.
Nerissa Ravencroft, take off your shirt.
Whoa, now.
That was that was you two! I don't know about that.
That was—that was you two! I don't know about that.
We also have pictures on the phone. I think you're mistaken. I would never speak that way to Princess.
So that we go we never gonna give her donuts ever again and you will never have donuts ever again.
So that we're never gonna give her donuts ever again, and you will never have donuts ever again.
And I would have never donuts? How did you know I died donuts?
And I would have never donuts? How did you know I liked donuts?
No more donuts!
But if you if you just confess, we have an in with Nerissa Raven Craft.
But if you just confess, we have an in with Nerissa Ravencroft.
Yeah, offer a good deal, we can give you what you want.
A date with the rest of Raven Craft!
A date with Nerissa Ravencroft!
Okay, now you guys witch trolls, this is the butler one.
Look, I admit it, I know who...
Answer right now!
Answer right now! Get her right now!
Go crazy! Go crazy on her!
I'm scared! Hey you!
A fat woman, it is my lucky day. Chief Raora.
Oh, Chief Raora, what do you guys think you're doing, huh?
I was doing what you were saying.
You useless! You gonna do anything in this place!
You useless! You won't do anything in this place!
Why did I hire you, huh? You're so useless.
We have all the evidence and you still didn't manage to make her tell the truth!
Chief, we tried our best, okay? We are on the verge of overwork!
Chief, we tried our best, okay? We're on the verge of overwork!
You're embarrassing us in front of the criminal!
Well, maybe you should do better than this.
You're not even listening to me, are you?
We never fix our coffee machine and we never get three-time off, Raora!
We never fix our coffee machine, and we never get free time off, Raora!
Well, if you work more, maybe you will deserve your coffee machine.
Do you like coffee?
No.
Well, what do you want from me?
I want April 10th!
Any quiet silence!
You know, one of my favorite vtuber entertainers is Cecilia Immergreen. She does not like coffee.
Do you remember what did you do in that record?
I I mean I I make up my own stories in my blog.
I—I mean, I—I make up my own stories in my blog.
Well, your own story with Nerissa Raven, how many times?
Well, your own story with Nerissa Ravencroft, how many times?
Get her boys! Get her wasp!
I think I think you're all with it, I'm leaving it on you guys, I think you're doing great.
I think—I think you're all with it. I'm leaving it on you guys. I think you're doing great.
So you do know Nerissa Ravencroft!
I know that her name is spelled backwards is a soy win.
I know that her name is spelled backwards, so I win.
How do you know that? How do you know that?
I know many wineworths, because I'm very popular well with the ladies.
I care about the photo collection she has in her room.
We have some things that I want to show you, okay?
This is paper right here. Hey, will you set my jack-o'-lanterns, please?
These are all the photos that we found in your room that you have taken of Nerissa Raven Craft.
These are all the photos that we found in your room that you have taken of Nerissa Ravencroft.
Photos! You recognize these photos?
Nurse's Raven Croft?
You took them. We found them on your camera.
I think my mother... wait, wait, we like... Smurf? We're so Raven Croft!
It was not your mother!
Oh!
There's a selfie right here!
Oh.
That's you! Right there!
What do you think?
That's you. That's you.
So, what do you have to say?
Is that you? Is that not you?
I think there's an imposter here.
Think about the evidence that we have, the bra with the wrong size so it's not hers, it's from Nurse's Raven Croft, because it's also signed by her.
We found a bra in your room.
It's the wrong size!
Yes. It's we I
I checked your breast size when you came in.
I would,
and it's not this size.
Bra- That one.
It is Nurse's Raven Croft.
And it's also blue! Tell her that it's blue! She never wears blue!
And we know you don't wear blue bras.
I do! You're sure you're not- I I checked.
I ya, I think you guys should I think you guys should wear this.
Stop it criminal!
I mean, we can- we can give you more than a bra from Nurse's Raven Croft.
We can give you way more than a bra from Nurse's Raven Croft.
(screaming / laughter)
It's too far up! It's too far up!
It's me!
She brought it!
That's her!
What are you doing to her?
What did you offer just now?
I was doing You were trying to be a snitch!
You were trying to be a snitch to the mini-ceri-ceri! Did you hurt me? It was all her!
When you when you're telling me to do
Time to get away!
She was talking about She was talking about the bra! You tried to- You tried to forget! No!
We are not- trying to find a new victim!
What do you want me to do?
(sigh)
What are you doing? Why am I even paying you right now?
I- All I do is just yell at- It's my first day on the force, and I just really wanted to be a good cop, and 99938383 is just too good, and we had all the evidences and all. She wore it just- She- It's so cute!
I've never seen such a thing. 9993X3XD was just so cunning and that was kind of attractive actually, those long hairs and those curves... I should- I should go find her.
Oh, they are totally useless. They can't do anything. I- I need to find new new people for this job. They don't have the guts for this. Yeah. But 9993X3XD, she said that she likes ladies and stuff. Maybe she will like me. Maybe she could work with me, who knows? Hm. What is she anyway?
Heh. They didn't see it coming. They didn't know I was uh well, they didn't know I was 9993X3XD. But they didn't- they didn't crack me one bit. For I am too good, I am too cunning, I am uh uh too too powerful, I say say. Can I get out of this?
The next training is Firearms Training.
What's required is precision and split-second judgment.
A moment's hesitation can greatly impact the outcome.
Can justice remain unphased by the situation and deliver highly accurate shots?
Firearms training, let's go!
First, let's go over the rules.
A variety of targets will appear one after another.
Your job is to quickly decide whether to shoot or hold your fire!
If it's a valid target, take it out with your revolver.
But be careful, not every target is meant to be shot.
Out of the 10 targets, 3 are no-shoot targets, so don't let your guard down!
Okay. Okay. Okay. I got it. What do you mean? I wasn't listening. I wasn't paying attention.
So we should everything.
No!
Okay, targets got everyone.
Did you not listen to what I said?
And most importantly, she'll be your friend.
What? What the freak? All right, sir.
Cecilia, you're up first! Just like that!
Justice, shoot shit down! Shoot shit down! Shoot shit down!
Cecilia
Cecilia, are you feeling confident?
Really good. Look at my trigger- oh, it's not- Oh, yeah, I'm really good.
I should shoot everything. Look! And I'm going to win.
Ready! Set!
Go!
You start.
Whoa!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Oh, I got it, I got it.
She's crazy!
Oh, my god! Is that a gnome?
With a mustache!
Did you kill the gnome?
Magical fairy mushrooms!
Magical fairy gnome!
Is that a pizza? Shoot the pizza! Shoot the pizza!
Wait, we weren't supposed to shoot the pizza?
Oh no! No! That was a mistake!
No, she was just a little guy!
No!
Die!
That was just a little girl! Oh, that's a royal guard!
Cecilia!
Oh, she's a kill--
Wait, wait, wait! He's texting while driving!
Good job. Good job. We got rid of a criminal.
Hey, that's my pension!
Oh yeah, shoot that! Shoot her pension!
Give me my pension back!
Oh gosh. Hello, tiny jetpack.
Hey, tiny jetpack! I got the shot!
A cucumber? Wait, cucumber! No, don't, don't, don't, don't eat cucumber!
Cucumber!
Yay! Pickle!
Wait, yeah, we -- yes. He's stealing the wrong cookies!
By the way.
I did it!
I shot everything!
Cecilia's final score is... 1, 7, 7! 67!
Hey wait. 89? Oh well.
Even if I -- even if I shot honestly,
I think the cucumber was a minus and I thought it was a plus, because we wanted to kill the cucumber so she doesn't have to eat it.
I don't like cucumbers, right?
And I think even if I shot the ones that we were meant to shoot sometimes,
You -- a crisis situation, you just have to make a decision even if it's the wrong one.
Shoot that!
Keep up, keep up.
Okay. Shoot it, shoot it, shoot it, shoot it, shoot it, shoot it, shoot it!
Oh, she's a true leader. Shoot her! Shoot her, shoot her, shoot her!
Oh, that's me! With a mustache! How can you shoot yourself?
Wait, that's obviously not -- No! That's a bird! That's a bird!
Well, that's a nice bird.
Ha ha ha! Shoot it again! Shoot it again!
Woah! Did you shoot your headshot? That would be a mistake if you do that.
Okay. Oh, penny. Ah, penny! Oh, penny is back over there. Wow! Huh?
Oh, that's a penny on the ground.
Wait, you were shooting the -- What's her?
Oh, my pension! We need -- We need, we need, we need, we need! Yes!
We need that for justice.
Oh, my pension! My pizza! I'm -- I'm hungry again.
No, no, no, no! Don't get a get -- Yeah, people are gonna get squeaky.
Okay. Give me money! Money!
Money! Money! We need that! We need money! We need money!
Bunny! What? What? We need bunnies! What?
Oh, no, Liz.
Oh, kill him. Kill him. That's a great --
Kill it. Kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it! That is so funny though.
What am I doing for? Shoot me! Shoot, shoot, shoot it, Liz!
Hello! Hello! Ah, gun, gun, gun!
Yeah! So good! Okay, you are done!
Oh, yes! Okay. Now, what is my score?
Drum roll... Nine! Nine? Nine!
No points?
No, no, no.
Nine! Oh, okay. Nine points! Wow! Okay.
Flame on.
Yosh! Yosh!
Your aim is so bad!
I just fell down. No! Liz! Liz!
How are you feeling, Gigi?
You confident?
I'm confident!
I'm confident! I'm confident. Get them. Okay, go.
Three, two, one, go!
Oh, oh!
That's a Corgi!
That was a Roselian! How could you?
Because I'm not real.
The sun's not real.
Money, money, money.
That's money.
That was good.
That's the money! Yay, money! Yay, money!
Okay. Keep shooting. Oh, money, money, money, money, money, money!
Money, money, money!
Perfect. We need money.
We need -- I have to kill her! Big success!
That was just a baby.
Kill the baby. I'm dead, mom.
Hey, get it, get it! Get the dead target.
Kill it! This is so tiny!
Yay!
No, dead-box!
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know? Did you know? Did you die? Did you die?
I can't hit it!
You're safe!
I hate it.
I think it's too fast.
You're lucky. You're lucky. You're so lucky right now.
Okay. Oh no!
Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
I can't kill it!
I looked into its eyes and I can't kill it!
And I looked, I looked right into its eyes and I couldn't do it!
Monster truck!
Yes! It's gone!
No more pizza!
No more pizza diet!
Wow! It's eating the royal cookies!
Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
That's not a real guy!
That's a real guy!
That's why it doesn't work!
Bro, he's texting while driving!
Oh my god, we have to put him down now!
He's so good!
Okay, I think you are done!
Okay, you've run out, you're running out of bullets now, okay?
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, we got it.
Save yourself!
Oh no, no, no!
Okay!
What is time to review? Gigi score!
It's so real! It's so real!
Okay, the final score for Gigi is...
Gun! Good!
You!
I'm so tired!
Hey! You got eight! You got eight!
You got eight!
Yay!
It's your turn, Raora Panthera.
It's me.
Yeah, yeah, big cat means...
Oh, big cat? Me?
Yeah, yeah, okay, okay, let's go.
Me?
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's face the gun!
It's not real!
None of that!
I practice so much!
What do I do again?
Uh, you sort of targets and you shoot the ones that are bad.
Bad targets!
Okay? Bad ones.
Bad, only the bad ones.
How do I know which one is bad?
That's up to you to decide as a member of Justice.
Ready! Ready!
Yes!
Set!
Go!
Yay!
Okay, okay, I got it. I got it.
Shoot that, I'm right there, Raora.
I'm right there.
A little too left, a little...
Raora, you were supposed to shoot this one!
Yeah, it's not shoot me, it's a little sad.
Raora with the god eyes, huh?
What kind of god eyes are those?
He can't handle it. He can't handle it.
Get him.
Get him! He's driving!
Get him!
No! That guy's a menace!
Next one for sure.
Liz! Liz, kill her!
Kill her!
You killed her!
I'm right here, Raora. That's an impostor!
Oh my god, you killed her! You killed Liz!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him! Kill him! Kill him! Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
That's not a real guy!
That's why it doesn't work!
Bro, he's texting while driving!
Oh my god, we have to put him down now!
He's so good!
Okay, I think you are done!
What kind of god eyes are those?
He's stealing the cookies!
Hey, but it's not a go.
Why didn't you kill the guy with the cookies?
Alright, next, Raora. You can get the next one.
You can do it. You can do it.
Aww, cute!
No, he's he's evil! He's stealing family mushrooms!
Family mushrooms?
He doesn't have mushrooms.
Hey, I thought he's a dad. He's a dad!
He doesn't have mushrooms!
Hey, I thought he's a dad!
Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
Oh, no, it's an egg!
An egg with the queen!
Oh, death-box!
Death-box! Death-box!
Get it, get it, get it, get it!
Oh, it was a death-box.
Jump, jump, jump! You can just jump!
You are the one I love! You are the one I love!
Oh, it jumps real, real high!
Cucumber!
Yay, cucumber!
Oh, money!
Money!
Do we want money? No.
Oh, no, we don't want money.
help the Gigi text.
I guess.
What's wrong with the G-text?
That was great!
That was that was that was great, Raora!
That was really good! That was that was that was really good, Raora!
That was really good!
Pretty good, wasn't it? Pretty good?
That was really fun, criminals.
Gigi, do you want to say the score?
I'll say the score, Raora.
You want to know how much it was?
I know.
Do you want to know?
Hold my hand, I need to tell you. Hold my hand.
It was 20. It was 4.
4!
Justice for 4! Justice for 4!
You did that on purpose 'cause there's four of us!
You're so You're so you're so clever, Perry!
You want a 4 because of Justice!
And with that, the training is complete!
And the winner is...
The winner is...
Elizabeth!
You're a loser, loser, loser, loser!
Yes I am! Go! She's a loser! It's okay, you're a loser!
We're everything loser!
We're everything losers!
I just wanted to make you win because I'm the strongest with my god eyes, so...
Because you're so cute! See? She looks good! I don't have a team behind my back.
What's that behind your back?
What's that! What's that! She made it!
Get them! Get them!
Look at that! Look at that!
The next training is Traffic Enforcement Training.
This duty requires accurately assessing the violation and processing it correctly.
However, in the field, unexpected behavior can sometimes shake an officer's judgment.
Can justice stay unfazed in any situation and carry out the appropriate response?
We did it, boys!
Good job, my goon.
We ran a red light right now!
My goon, do the voice! Do the voice!
Okay, boss.
Good afternoon.
Well, saw this then? You know what?
I pulled you over.
That was really cool!
Oh my god, you did it again. Silencio.
Don't act like you don't know anything! You blew right through the stop sign!
We're not liars! We're in a rush!
My husband, he's pregnant!
Can I see your driver's license, please?
Yes, yes.
Do you have your driver's license? Do you have your driver's license?
We don't have time! He's really pregnant! I am so pregnant!
His water just broke, and we have to go to the hospital!
And we have to go to the hospital right now, please!
We're not! We're not lying! He's like really pregnant!
Look how big he is! I think she's not...
Flagrant answer.
Excuse me, my husband is really pregnant, he's really big right now.
I'm really pregnant!
Please. Let me feel the baby.
It's kicking! I don't know, can you not feel it? My son! I feel you! You're El! Silencio.
Please, don't you think those are two to our acting, Elena? Mamamia.
Please, don't you think those are too true to our acting, Elena? Mamamia.
Do you think? Could it be?
Yes. See? This is exactly what I was thinking.
My son! No, no, no!
You are always stopping us because I am so pregnant!
Yes! You were speeding! It was with the baby! It was with the baby!
There was a horse there! No, it was my baby! It was our baby recently!
I heard the squeals! Our baby coming from the truck! Hey, you can't say that about my baby!
Mandyfree, take a look! I do mind! I do mind!
Wait, wait, wait, wait! No, no, no, no!
Get the gun! Get the gun!
Please! You are definitely guilty!
No, you can't! Open the shell! Stop! Officer, please! Officer, please!
You'll stop me? It's a horse!
It's a horse! It's a horse! It's my son! No, it's our steed, Cecilia Marin!
Cecilia Emerine, you're under arrest! No! We didn't do anything! Arrested!
I can't be under arrest! I had too much to lose! Yeah, you're under arrest! Give me your hand!
You're under arrest, officially! Wait! Boss! Boss! You can't leave me!
I'm the boss, yes! You're under arrest with her! We did nothing!
We're going to get him! Get out! Let's get her! I can't drive!
It's just you and me, baby.
National Museum
[Location: National Museum]
All right, the place is empty.
Got about 10 minutes before the guards next patrol.
So, this is the Yagoo trophy...
The Giga-Mega National Treasure.
I'm gonna make a fortune on this!
This is Justice.
Is this an emergency?
Help! Please, please, somebody—
please, somebody, help me right now!
I don't know what to do!
Calm down, and take a deep breath.
Can you tell me exactly what happened?
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Help! Help!
Please! Please help me!
Ah, calm down.
Calm down.
Help me!
Leave it to us,
leave it to us.
Justice is on the way
right now!
Everyone, we have a case.
The ultimate national treasure has been stolen!
Head to the scene, immediately!
The ultimate national treasure?
You mean the Yagoo statue?
Who even wants that?
Just let him keep it!
Gigi Murin
Gigi, that is disrespectful!
It is still the ultimate national treasure.
We're counting on you.
Fine,
I'm on it.
Halloween!
Leaves!
Ha!
The super limited edition Sanrio Tiny Plush is dropping in just 3 minutes!
It's limited quantity, okay?
That means I absolutely have to buy it!
Okay, so, only 2 minutes left now.
Just go already!
No, a minute! Per l'ultimo!
Raora Panthera
Cecilia, did you get any information?
Ceciliaaaaa!
Hold on!
Who the hell changed the camera channel?
Cecilia Immergreen
Glad you loved my present, Cece!
This was you?! You little piece of shit!
You absolute garbage can! When I get you, I'm going to...
Cecilia, every second counts here.
I know, I know.
All right, found a backdoor in the palace server, cracking the encrypted protocol via brute force,
and forcing the security patch overdrive on the mainframe system security data...
Fine. I mean...
The suspect is a woman dressed entirely in black.
Height looks around 168 centimeters. She really likes people wearing helmets.
She's fleeing north!
If you move now, you can still catch her!
You all heard her!
Let's move out and apprehend the suspect!
For Justice!
Justice!
Raora, what are you doing?
You're not even driving!
You don't know how to drive a car?
Put your foot on the gas pedal!
Wait, wait, wait!
What?
There is a horse in front of us!
There's no freaking horse!
There is a freaking horse!
Oh, my god, there's a freaking horse!
Oh, there's a horse right there!
Oh!
No way, there's a real horse!
Get us out of here!
Now, how are we supposed to get out of here now?
Holy fuck!
Am I even going to be able to make it to Dizzy's and Cecilia's for Halloween since it's Halloween?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Horse is like vegetables, right?
I think there's a cucumber in the trunk.
A cucumber? A cucumber in the trunk?
What about the horse? Dizzy, hold on!
Why do you have a cucumber in your pocket right now?
Dizzy Marihisa, you know why.
You know why.
What?
Dizzy and you know I hate cucumbers.
Why do you have a cucumber right now?
Ew! Get out of here!
You know what I'm going to put the cucumber?
Where?
Get out of here now! I don't want to see the cucumber. Ew!
What about the horse? What about the horse?
No! What about the horse?
Don't you hate me? Don't you fucking hate me?
You hate me so you hate me.
Just say it! Tell me! You fucking hate me!
Tell me that you bring cucumbers and that I know that I hate and that I hate.
We talked about that many times and now
Those two are away with the fairies.
Cecilia, do you have any updates on the suspect's location?
So close.
Pre-register Now
Cecilia?
Cecilia Immergreen!
No! I missed!
Look what you did, Liz! You ruined my perfect score! What's up, close?!
Not you too!
Did I fail them as a mother?
My heart breaks as their big sister.
I've done everything in my power to look after those three.
Those three wild, eccentric little sisters and guide them to this very day.
I gave them my all.
What did I do to deserve such cruelty?
Where did I go wrong?
Where did my guidance stray away from the path?
You three were still still there, huh? Huh?
Yeah.
We're sorry.
Big sister, I will be a good girl.
Big sister.
Big sister, big sister, big sister.
It's just allergies. I'm not crying. You're crying.
Thank you, big sister.
Happier than ever.
Just is just like that.
Guys, everyone!
It's Dizzy who stole the ultimate Yago statue!
We're going to kill them!
What the freak? Kill them, kill them!
Hey, you! Hold it right there!
Because of you, I missed out on a limited edition Zucchini, and I didn't even get to eat my delicious pizza!
How are you going to take responsibility for this?
That sounds like a you problem. Go eat your pizza now.
Oh, by the way, there's a shop nearby famous for its cucumber pizza.
It's to die for.
Cucumber pizza?
Yeah.
Ew!
Even I've had it before. Absolutely exquisite.
This is This is such an insult! Impossible!
It's okay. It's okay. Don't worry, relax. Relax, relax.
Doom!
DOOM!
JUSTICE SHOPPING
Justice 2nd Anniversary Merch!
First, take a look at this.
The premium acrylic message board.
We spoke with someone who actually used it.
Oh, you want to meet?
You talk about the premium acrylic message board?
Ah yeah, yeah, sure. Um, oui, oui.
Ah, this artwork is so cool! I love it so much.
Ah, using acrylic instead of paper was such a good choice!
And it makes it feel really special.
And the foil stamped replicated messages...
that's honestly the best part!
I can't stop looking at it.
It just looks that much good, you know?
Ah, please support Justice and buy their merch. Oui, thank you. Merci.
Wow, that's some pretty high praise!
We've still got lots more merch to introduce, so let's move on to the next item. Here it is!
Ta-da! This is Raora Panthera,
the artist behind the embroidered keychains!
Rawr!
You know, I'm so happy I got the chance to draw for my Justice girls.
Creating something for my friends always feels really special.
And I hope you're gonna love them as much as I do.
Yes, yes, yes.
And you know, they took all my adorable illustrations and turned them into those cute embroidered keychains.
And, you know, since they're keychains, you can attach them to your bag and take them with you wherever you go.
Yeah, a little bit extra cuteness for your everyday life.
So make sure to pick one up, and trust me, the cuteness is guaranteed.
Yes! Look at that! They're so cute! Adorable!
What a wonderful piece of merch! Anyone would love to have that one in their home, including me!
All right, let's move on to the next piece of merch. Take a look at this!
Hm? You want to hear about the badge? Heh, of course.
My sweethearts, my Justice chat,
this badge was designed with the image of law enforcement and authority in mind.
The weighty, prestigious look fits Justice perfectly, don't you think?
I think it looks absolutely fantabidosi. It looks fantastic! Very cool.
Anyone who strives for Justice should definitely get their hands on one.
Oh, and it also comes in a beautiful display box, so it's perfect for displaying and admiring as well.
I hope when you guys look at your medal, or wear it, that you will remember how us, Justice, are, and that we're so proud of you all, and we all really appreciate you so, so, so much.
So I really hope that comes to mind every time you wear or look at this medal.
And that was a message from Elizabeth! And now, for the final item we're introducing today, here it is!
Wait! A Justice show? Oh, oh my god! Oh my god, I'm so excited!
You want to hear my thoughts on this merch as the biggest Justice fan in the world? That has nothing to do with Justice, I'm just a random fan passing by!
Of course I'd know anything!
Q: What do you think about this item?
Oh, I absolutely love the design! The patches inspired by all four members of Justice are so cute and stylish.
And I love how each one of them reflects their personality. And the logo and the text on the back gives it such a cool, premium look. It's the kind of hoodie that it instantly makes you think...
Yes, this is Justice!
Q: How is it when you actually wear it?
Oh, it's amazing! The brushed fleece lining makes it super warm and comfortable.
Not only does it look great, but it's also really practical. And the fact that it comes in both L and LL sizes is fantastic!
I think a lot of fans will appreciate having different size options, so make sure to buy the Justice merch, okay?
Wow, jolly good! Now that's a passionate fan! And that's it for Justice Shopping.
Ta-da!
So, how was it?
It was awesome.
And what did you like the most?
The... horse!
Oh, the horse...
And there's just this new... flash!
We interrupt your regularly scheduled programming to bring you this breaking news.
We have just received an exclusive update from Justice, the Global Guardians of Peace.
Rumor has it, a brand new track from the iconic Four-Piece is about to drop at any second.
I repeat: new music from Justice is imminent; do not touch that dial.
We will be right back with the world premiere. This is Kronii signing out.
Yeah!
Are you there?
You're a SUPER GIRL!
(JUSTICE, JUST LIKE THAT!)
(JUSTICE, GET GET THAT!)
If you're feeling trapped, send out a signal right above!
(Gesundheit!)
We'll find you, set you free then you can sign up for the club!
(In it!)
Danger, fun fun fun
Soul shine like the sun
(MINNA HAPPINESS, MINNA HAPPINESS)
The frig? I'm big! My strong strong muscle
They see me run, it's no miracle
You are shining, SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing, LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL!
I'm the SUPER!
(Hey!)
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER! (Hey!) DUPER!
SUPER! DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
Come sing with us, beating villains for fun <3 it
(I'M SUPER GIRL)
Put on your antennas, get your super girl fit
(YOU'RE SUPER GIRL)
I'm the SUPER!
(Hey!)
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
I always want a pizza, stack those fries up to the sky
(Ciao ciao)
You lot say whatcha think about us hittin' town tonight?
(Justice!)
Feeling happy time, no sad, say bye bye
(MOTTO MANIAC, JUSTICE JUST LIKE THAT)
So stomp, stomp, stomp your feet to this beat
Cuz we are space, no no gravity!
You are shining, SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing, LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL!
I'm the SUPER!
(Hey!)
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER! (Hey!) DUPER!
SUPER! DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
I know you're feeling so super bad
You don't have depression, you're just super sad
We are change the world, that's hope!
If you doubt, hope you explode!
Justice loud, Justice proud and we keep telling you!
(K, adlib!)
We are SUPER!
(Hey!)
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER! (Hey!) DUPER!
SUPER! DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
Justice we are justice, make the baddies go boom!
(I'M SUPER GIRL)
Come on, come on, baby, rocket ship to the moon!
(YOU'RE SUPER GIRL)
I'm the SUPER!
(Hey!)
DUPER!
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
And that was "Supernova Super Girl", our brand new song!
And just like that, our second anniversary stream is coming to an end.
So, what did you all think? We'll start with Raora this time.
And me? Yeah, you first this time.
Ah, it was really fun. It was amazing. I can't believe it's been already two years, like...
I know!
Ah, thank you so much you guys as well for being the best...
the best companions ever, you know?
Yeah!
I'm so grateful to you guys and thank you to Just Chat...
for supporting us since two years now. It's insane. Can you take just chat...
Thank you Just Chatting!
Thank you very much, everyone!
Thank you very much for being here today, everyone! Thank you for two years! Stay Justice!
Please keep supporting us and listen to our song!
Stream Supernova as well, okay?
What am I thinking?
I think this stage is very cool! Look at this stage! Wow!
And look at this amazing team. I can't ask for a better...
We love you all very much!
And just as we love you all very much too, thank you so much for supporting Justice. Thank you so, so, so much!
We love you so much!
So many gifts, you guys are so spoiled.
Are you reading chat? Are you reading chat? Oh my god!
Stay Justice! Thank you for the party for two years! Two!
We didn't even know... I didn't even know Raora could count up to two! Really, really!
But we made it to two years!
Thank you for the partying on! Please stream Supernova Super Girl!
Learn the chants!
For some reason, maybe you should learn the chants.
I wonder if there's a lyric somewhere for you to learn when we go...
Supernova Super Girl!
Mina happiness!
We all feel like Supergirls because of you guys. Thank you so much!
And don't forget to grab the merch! Purchase our merch!
Yes, thank you, thank you. Thank you all so much for celebrating with us today! Please keep supporting Justice, please, going forward as well.
Now then, let's all say goodbye together with our own chants!
Justice! Just like that! Justice! Get, get, down!
Mina happiness! Mina happiness!
yeah
are you there？
Are you there?
you're a super girl
(justice just like that , justice get get that)
(Justice just like that, justice get, get that)
if you're feeling trapped , send out a signal right above！
If you're feeling trapped, send out a signal right above!
(gesundheit！)
(Gesundheit!)
we'll find you , set you free then you can sign up for the club！
We'll find you, set you free then you can sign up for the club!
(in nit！)
(Innít!)
danger , fun fun fun
Danger, fun, fun, fun.
no sad , say bye bye
No sad, say bye-bye.
(minna happiness , minna happiness)
(Minna happiness, minna happiness)
the frig？ i'm big！ my strong strong muscle
The frig? I'm big! My strong, strong muscle.
they see me run , it's no miracle
They see me run, it's no miracle.
you are shining
so bright！
So bright!
do your dancing
let's fight！
Let's fight!
you can be a
super super girl
i'm the
super！
Super!
(hey！)
(Hey!)
duper！
Duper!
(supernova super girl)
super！
Super!
(hey！)
(Hey!)
duper！
Duper!
(supernova super girl)
come sing with us , beating villains for fun <3 it
Come sing with us, beating villains for fun, love it.
(i'm super girl)
put on your antennas , get your super girl fit
Put on your antennas, get your super girl fit.
(you're super girl)
super！
Super!
(hey！)
(Hey!)
duper！
Duper!
supernova super girl